<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<!--
 * IceStream - The Official IceFilms Android Application
 * Copyright (C) 2011-2013 Stonyx
 *
 * The IceStream application (and any "covered work" as defined by the GNU General Public
 * License Version 3) is licensed under the GNU General Public License Version 3 (henceforth
 * referred to as "GNU GPL V3") with the following amendments that supersede any relevant wording
 * in the GNU GPL V3:
 *
 * 1. The IceStream application (and any "covered work" as defined by the GNU GPL V3) can be
 *    statically and/or dynamically linked to any source code, library, or application developed
 *    or released by Stonyx (the original authors of the IceStream application), regardless of the
 *    type of license that such source code, library, or application is licensed under.
 *
 * 2. The IceStream application (and any "covered work" as defined by the GNU GPL V3) can not be
 *    distributed for a fee without the prior written consent provided by Stonyx (the original
 *    authors of the IceStream application).
 *
 * The preceding amendments make up part of the license that the IceStream application is licensed
 * under.  They apply to and need to be included (along with the GNU GPL V3) with any derivative
 * work as outlined in the GNU GPL V3.
 *
 * This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; 
 * without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.
 * See the GNU GPL V3 for more details.
 *
 * You should have received a copy of the GNU GPL V3 along with this program.  If not, see
 * http://www.gnu.org/licenses/.
-->

<resources>
  <string name="app_name">Ice Stream</string>
  <string name="main_home">Home</string>
  <string name="main_tv_shows">TV Shows</string>
  <string name="main_movies">Movies</string>
  <string name="main_music">Music</string>
  <string name="main_stand_up">Stand-Up</string>
  <string name="main_other">Other</string>
  <string name="main_invalid_url_error">The URL specified in Preferences for the IceFilms website
      is invalid.</string>

  <string name="browse_retry">Try Connecting Again</string>
  <string name="browse_progress">Please wait while we retrieve information from IceFilms.</string>
  <string name="browse_page_download_error">An error occurred while downloading information from
      IceFilms.</string>
  <string name="browse_page_timeout_error">Unable to connect to IceFilms. IceFilms might be down
      currently.</string>
  <string name="browse_image_download_error">An error occurred while downloading this item\'s
      image.</string>
  <string name="browse_image_decode_error">An error occurred while decoding this item\'s
      image.</string>
  <string name="browse_image_timeout_error">Unable to connect to the server hosting this item\'s
      image. That server might be down currently.</string>
  <string name="browse_parse_error">An error occurred processing information from IceFilms.</string>
  <string name="browse_database_error">Unable to connect to the IceFilms database. IceFilms might
      be down currently.</string>

  <string name="help_help">
    Note: Please also install MoboPlayer, MX Video Player, or VPlayer to take full advantage of
    Ice Stream.\n
    \nIce Stream allows you to quickly and easily browse and watch the thousands of TV shows and
    movies cataloged by the IceFilms website. Simply choose a category when you first open the
    application and start browsing the huge collection of videos available to you. Once you find
    something you want to watch, choose one of the file sources. You will be given a choice to open
    the file by streaming it, open the file after first downloading it, or just download and save
    the file.\n
    \nIn order to play the video files you will need to have an application installed on your
    device that supports the DivX file format. Most devices will require the installation of one of
    the many free media players available for the Android platform. Not all media players have support
    for file streaming and these will require that the file first be downloaded. Three full featured
    media players that support the DivX file format and have streaming support are MoboPlayer,
    MX Video Player, and VPlayer. We highly recommend that you install one of these media players to
    take full advantage of Ice Stream.\n
    \nTechnical Notes: DivX formated files usually use the avi file extension, however, the avi
    file extension is also used for other file formats. The default video player installed on most
    devices supports the avi file extension, however, it does not support the DivX file format.
    Therefore if you try to play DivX files using the default video player it will result in the
    video player producing an error message. Also note that if the only media player installed on
    your device does not support the avi file extension or does not support streaming (and you
    choose to open the file by streaming it) you will receive an error message letting you know that
    no application is installed on your device that can open the file. To rectify all of these
    issues, we highly recommend you install one of the media players recommended above.
  </string>
  <string name="help_support">
    If you require further assistance or have\n
    any comments, suggestions, or complaints\n
    about this application please feel free\n
    to post on the Ice Stream Support Thread\n
    on the Ice Films Forum.
  </string>
  <string name="help_about">
    %1$s Version %2$s\n
    www.icefilms.info
  </string>
  <string name="help_disclaimer">
    Disclaimer: None of the videos available through this application are hosted by Ice Films. The
    Ice Stream application is a mobile front end for the Ice Films website which is a catalog of
    videos available on MegaUpload and 2Shared. Please direct any legal inquiries to the MegaUpload
    or 2Shared corporations who own the servers on which these videos are hosted.
  </string>
</resources>